Err, Speerio Rosa Burosa.
Sumomo, this Recipe is...
Yes.
A Recipe that emits warmth which gives courage and confidence.
Speerio Rosa Burosa
Wah, amazing!
That's great, Sumomo!
Let's go, Yuki-chan.
We're doing this quite fast...
Should we wait until it actually drops down?
It's alright.
Just watch, Yuki-chan.
Puruvu Radi
Amazing, Sumomo!
You've been getting really good at this.
It's all thanks to you, Yuki-chan.
One more remaining, right?
What's the matter?
After gathering all the star drops...
You'll go back home, right, Yuki-chan?
Huh? Ah... Yes...
I'll be lonely when that time comes...
Sumomo...
Sorry for suddenly being sad.
I'll do my best, so look forward to it.
Akihime would never have thought, not even in her dreams...
that Yuki-chan's real identity... is Tsuwabuki Masaharu.
So now six star drops have been collected.
Soon you'll no longer be Yuki-chan.
How about staying as Yuki-chan, since he is really cute.
Think about me for a second!
So then, what kind of advice do you need?
I want to tell her that Yuki-chan is actually me.
You don't want to lie to your girlfriend?
M-My girlfriend?!
You don't have to feel embarrassed...
that both you and Akihime are officially a couple in love.
It's good to be young!
However, it won't be long before all seven star drops are gathered.
So wouldn't it be better telling her after that?
I feel as if I'm deceiving Akihime.
I want to tell her the truth as soon as possible!
Well, I do understand how you feel.
But, you must never do that, Tsuwabuki-kun.
Something that can never be reversed will happen.
Something that can never be reversed?
If Yuki-chan's identity is known to Sumomo-chan...
I guess I'll have to wait until we gather all seven star drops.
U-Umm...
Akihime.
Good morning, Haru-kun.
Sumomo?
You just called him Haru-kun, right?
She did, she did!
So madly in love, aren't they?
Haru, your reply?
Don't tell me you're going to say "Akihime"?
It's just natural to use her first name when you were just called by yours.
Go Haru-kun! Be courageous and say it!
Sumomo!
Ah, too bad.
Such good timing too!
The ion exchange resin is...
It's good if I can do that...
calling her Sumomo...
Miss, what is the matter? Miss?!
Miss!
Timu Forna Mei...
Such a high level Recipe used by that girl.
Without working so hard just because she is Karin-sama's daughter...
Timu Forna Mei.
I can do it too!
Nako-chan, you can't go home together with me after club activities today, right?
Today I have to go to the dojo, so...
What is it?
I was just thinking about visiting Nona-chan on the way home.
Since she hasn't been coming to class for a few days now...
and I'm worried about her.
Akihime...
To Akihime, Yuuki is her rival in gathering the star drops, but...
Because Akihime is like that...
Right now, I honestly feel that I can call her by her first name.
Umm, can I join in too, Su-
Su? So what is after the Su, Haru?
Come on, say it! Say it!
Don't be shy now.
Hey you guys, stop teasing them.
We aren't teasing them.
Yeah, that's right, we aren't.
We're just giving them our moral support!
Go, go! Haru-tan, do your best!
And I just said no teasing them.
Guess it's impossible in school.
One more time!
Timu Forna Mei!
Wow!
What a nice mansion!
Y-Yeah.
E-Err, the entrance bell is...
Sumomo!
Nako-chan!
I got permission to get off early.
Nako-chan.
I wanted to visit Yuuki-san too. Is that alright?
Yep!
Y-Yes!
H-Hello, this is Tsuwabuki.
Tsuwabuki-kun? You came at the right time!
Welcome!
Umm, we're here...
Tsuwabuki-kun!
Tsuwabuki-kun, please help!
Can I have some of your transformation potion?
Since Miss doesn't want to listen to anything at the moment.
Uhh, what do you mean?
Ah! Those ears!
Yes, I was trying to put the potions in batches when this accident happened...
So it was you!
Yes?
I ended up taking the wrong juice when I bumped into you at school!
Because of that, I change to a sheep doll at night!
Err... Tsuwabuki-kun, you're not from Figurare?
No! I changed to a sheep doll because of the potion that you dropped!
Ehh?! I am so sorry!
What have I done to Miss's classmate!?
Please forgive me!
It's okay.
Umm, you are forgiving me?
Well yeah, since it wasn't all that bad.
Thank you very much!
Well, I will call Miss.
I am here.
Miss.
Nona-chan!
Are you feeling better now?
Everyone was worried about you.
Here are some flowers.
Thank you for the flowers!
Nona-chan...
I don't want to be called that name by you.
Speerio Sharuruze Wein
I am Saint Aspalas' Prima, Prima Aspalas!
Let's do our last battle today!
Come, Prima Plam!
Yuuki...
Nako-chan!
I'll leave Haru-kun to you!
Hey, Yaeno! Hey!
Tsuwabuki, I'll explain later.
That's not what I mean. I'm...
Speerio Rosa Burosa
So you even know the transformation Recipe now too.
Well, you're becoming more and more of a worthy opponent.
Arthur! The vial.
Yes, Miss.
The star drops...
Miss, what are you doing...?
Wah, the star drops are...
Now, which of us can capture the star drops!?
Time to fight!
Paradivu Mei!
I won't let you!
Aquavu Puruvida!
Puruvi Radius!
She used the water to lure the star drops?
And capturing three of them at once!
Aspalas-san is amazing, after all.
Let me go, Yaeno!
Let me go to Akihime.
No!
Yaeno...
Akihime!
Yaeno.
Tsuwabuki, I cannot let you go.
Even if it means I have to use force.
Yaeno...
If you work hard, you will gain power.
I thought that's how it went.
But you on the other hand receive new powers just by doing it without any practice.
W-What do you mean?
I will not approve of that!
You're the only person I don't want to lose to!
Never!
I have to let Yuki-chan return to the Doll Land too.
There's no way that I'll lose!
Timu Forna Mei!
This is...
Right, a Recipe that can slow down time.
I can do it too.
Patis Aqua Omis!
I've got it now!
I have to do my best!
For Yuki-chan's sake!
Tamo Rei!
I'm back to normal!
You must be kidding! From that far away?!
I won't let you do that!
Again!
Timu Forna Mei!
It can't be!
Unbelievable!
Timu Forna...
This is...
Don't tell me I screwed up?
Miss, watch out!
It'll be dangerous if you keep on casting that spell!
That's right, Aspalas-san.
That Recipe is not normal!
I can do this.
Timu Forna Mei!
Miss!
Aspalas-... No! Nona-chan!
Nona-chan!
Akihime!
You can't.
What are you doing?!
I will not stand by and do nothing while Akihime is in trouble!
Tsuwabuki, if anything happens to you, Sumomo will be sad.
I want to be Sumomo's strength too!
But... I cannot, so...
I can. There's something that I can do!
Eh?
Because I have always been with Akihime gathering the star drops.
Tsuwabuki, how do you know about the star drops...?
Tsuwabuki!
Nona-chan!
Where are you?
Please say something, Nona-chan!
T-This is....
Please help!
The two of them are inside!
Inside this?
Sumomo...
Sumomo!
Sumomo! Sumomo!
You must never do that, Tsuwabuki-kun.
If your real identity is known to Sumomo-chan,
you will cease to move, think or speak.
You will become just a normal doll.
Forever...
Sumomo!
Sumomo, you can do it!
You're right, Yuki-chan.
I have to do my best.
I have to help Nona-chan.
That's right! If I use that chant...
Timu Forna Mei!
Sumomo!
Yuki-chan?
Are you alright?
Haru-kun.
Sumomo, slow down time.
It's the same chant as last time.
You should be able to slow down the wind.
Why do you know that, Haru-kun?
Quickly!
I tried to, but I can't...
You can do it. You can do it, Sumomo.
You definitely can do it.
Just be calm.
Do your best, Sumomo.
Timu Forna Mei!
I did it.
Sumomo, there!
Nona-chan!
The wind was caused by this Ladle?
Sumomo!
The Ladle is hot.
What should I do?
Let's try again.
Nako-chan.
Why...?
I wanted to do something for you too, Sumomo.
Not just watching you but something like what Tsuwabuki does.
Miss! Miss get a hold of yourself!
Miss!
I'm so glad you're okay!
Matsuda.
What happened to me?
This thing went berserk and caused that big whirlwind.
Sumomo went into it and saved you.
W-Why?
Because Sumomo is a kind girl.
So Haru-kun is... Haru-kun is Yuki-chan, right?
I'm sorry for lying until now.
No. I'm always being helped by Yuki-chan.
And seeing Haru-kun's face at school makes me feel better.
Haru-kun, thanks for everything...
Haru-kun?
Haru-kun!
Sorry, Su-mo-mo...
Yuki-chan?
What's wrong? Hey.
Haru-kun?
T-Tsuwabuki...
Hey! Come on, please say something!
Haru-kun!
Time is really precious, right?
Why can't it be like a game where you can just reload and try again?
But I heard that you can return, though.
What, what?
What do you mean?
Well, I don't really know myself.
What is that!?